TAYLOR ST JEAN

(Personal information redacted for public copy)

PHYSICS AND ENGINEERING STUDENT

Currently studying at North Seattle College to obtain my Associate of Science degree. Relevant completed coursework includes Engineering Physics 221-223, Calculus I-III, Chemistry 161, and the full English Composition series. Plans after obtaining an AS include pursuing a Bachelor of Science degree at a four-year university, eventually acquiring a Doctorate in the field of physics. Limited working proficiency in French.

EDUCATION

NORTH SEATTLE COLLEGE

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE - IN PROGRESS

· Currently enrolled and actively studying to obtain my Associate of Science Track 2 degree, which is specifically designed for Physics and Engineering majors.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BRN ENGINEERING

ELECTRICAL DRAFTER · APRIL 2022 - PRESENT

· After six months of working as an intern at the firm, I was offered a full position as an electrical drafter. I am primarily tasked with generating drawings in AutoCAD, however a portion of the position is spent working directly with the engineer who is teaching me to create my own solutions and eventually become a designer.

NORTH SEATTLE COLLEGE

LAB ASSISTANT · MARCH 2022 – PRESENT

• This is a State Work Study position I obtained at North Seattle College. At this job, I am tasked with general housekeeping work at the lab, such as cleaning used equipment and glassware, taking chemical inventory, and preparing demonstrations for science classes. Additionally, I am given the opportunity to work with the professors and learn more about chemistry through various experiments.

ERA LIVING

FOOD SERVER/HOST · DEC 2018 - PRESENT (PER DIEM)

• Duties include serving in the dining room during service, taking and filling orders and managing my time effectively to reduce wait times for the resident. As a host, I act as lead, assigning duties to all others working that night. Valuable skills I have learned on the job include communication with the blind and hard of hearing, the formation of interpersonal relationships, and effective communication with peers.

SKILLS

Technical: Microsoft Office/Excel, Linux, Python, HTML/CSS, Computer Hardware

Safety: Fire Prevention and Response, Medical Triage, CPR/AED, First Aid

STEM: Physics, Circuitry, Mathematics, Basic Chemistry

 References	/Project	Portfolio	available	upon	request
Kererences/	rioject	POLUOIO	avanabie	upon	request